QUINTON PRICE

COMPUTER SCIENCE STUDENT

PERSONAL PROFILE

Self-motivated student with a passion for software development and the outdoors. Experience with JavaScript, HTML, React, CSS, git, C++, Python and more. Hoping to gain experience in software development and learn new languages by working with skilled developers.

CONTACT INFORMATION

E-mail: quintonp10@gmail.com

Phone: (253) 310-7627

Website: <u>aprice.net</u>

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/quinton-price

GitHub: github.com/QuintonPrice

SKILLS

- React
- JavaScript
- Google Firebase
- CSS / HTML
- C++
- Python
- Java
- git
- Bootstrap
- Web APIs
- Active Directory / SCCM

EDUCATION

Walla Walla University

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science | Business Administration Minor

09/2019 - 06/2023

Relevant Courses:

- Fundamentals of Programming I & II (C++)
- Web Development (JavaScript, React)
- Assembly Language (ARM)
- Compilers
- Android App Development (Java)
- Digital Logic
- Dean's List Fall Quarter 2020

NOTABLE PROJECTS

- <u>Personal Portfolio</u> Website which serves as a personal portfolio. Built with React. Features include blog post components that read JSON info, mobile scaling, and more. Uses Netlify to automatically build/deploy website on each push to the Git repository.
- Trail App React website which will serve as a hiking and mountain biking trail repository. Users will have the ability to create accounts, add trails, create favorites, and more. Utilizes Google FireBase, Google Authentication, Netlify, and more.
- Android Travel App Android app written in Java that gives
 users the ability to see destinations near them (with search
 filters), look up information about locations, use Google Maps,
 and more.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Website Manager & Trip Leader

Walla Walla University | 02/21 - present

- Manage trip booking website with Flybooks and all relevant processes for outdoor recreation department that serves a student body of over 2,000 people
- Planned and lead outdoor trips with groups of 5 30 people several times per quarter

Help Desk Analyst I

Mutual of Enumclaw | 03/2020 - 01/2021, 06/2021 - 09/2021

- Collaborates with members of the IT team, assists with various departmental projects, provides on-call and rotational assignment support.
- Responds to, diagnoses and tracks/documents problems with users at a company with over 400 employees
- Identifies, innovates and suggests new procedures, and/or opportunities to streamline IT Department processing and record-keeping systems and practices.

Help Desk Intern

Mutual of Enumclaw | 06/2019 - 09/2019

- Provides front line support for PC hardware, software, peripheral devices, and network connectivity support for users.
- Images PCs over network & configures BIOS settings
- Maps network drives, installs advanced programs and works with network
- Experience using BMC Remedyforce Console, Track-IT and Active Directory